Guide to the Johan Kugelberg punk collection, circa 1974-1986.
Kugelberg, Johan punk collection
- Series II. Fliers and Posters
  - Dogs, The, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Notes: With ms. on verso - note from "Justin" to "Dr. Gerry Bronnstein." On the recto, Hoi Polloi's name is pasted on, obscuring the name of a different band.
  - Dr. Feelgood, 1975; 29.75 x 19.75 in. (Box 40)
    Location: UK
    Additional bands or artists: Kokomo, Chilli Willi
    Main text: Admit two - Naughty Rhytms UK '75 tour - Naughty Rhythms - Dr. Feelgood, Kokomo, Chilli Willi
    Notes: Promotional poster for 1975 pub rock tour.
  - Dream Syndicate, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: The Bangs, The Brat
    Main text: Tuesday Sept. (21st) - Dream Syndicate …
  - Drones, The, 1977; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: The Squat
    Additional bands or artists: The Negatives, Willie Hamilton's No Chord Trash
    Main text: Stuff the Joobly Special - Presenting The Drones …
    Notes: Double-sided flier; verso advertises the Drones' forthcoming EP "The Temptations of a White Collar Worker."
  - Esmerelda, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Venue: 18 Club
    Main text: Esmerelda - Around midnight, 18 Club
  - Ethyl Eichelberger, 8.5 x 14 in. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Artist: Peter Hujar (photo)
    Venue: Pyramid
    Main text: Ethyl Eichelberger at the Pyramid
    Notes: Wheatpasted poster.
  - Evening Standard [newspaper], ca. 1977-78; 28.75 x 17 in. (Box 40)
    Main text: Police move in on punk disc shops
    Notes: Poster advertising an Evening Standard headline story from ca. 1977-78 on a UK crackdown on record stores selling punk records.
  - Exploited, The, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Additional bands or artists: Battalion of Saints, 7 Seconds, Freeze, Tales of Terror
    Main text: Goldenvoice presents by popular demand!!! From England - The Exploited …
  - Exploited, The, 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Venue: Mendiolas Ballroom
    Additional bands or artists: Channel 3, Youth Brigade, Vandals, Aggression, Suicidal Tendencies
    Main text: Youth Movement '83 - Golden Voice & BYO present - Direct from England - Only L.A. appareance - The Exploited …
  - Eye Protection, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Artist: Roger I. Reyes, Julie Stein (photo)
    Additional bands or artists: Young Canadians, Feederz
    Main text: Eye Protection and Young Canadians from Canada with Feederz from Arizona
  - Fabulous Fascinations, 1966; 11 x 17 in. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Venue: 321 Divisadero
    Additional bands or artists: Demon Lovers
    Main text: The fabulous fascinations, The demon lovers
  - Fall, The, 1980s; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Venue: Myron's Ballroom
    Additional bands or artists: Blurt, The Flesheaters
    Main text: Phantom + Bunko productions presents - from England - The Fall, Blurt, The Flesheaters
  - Fall, The, 1977; 42 x 30 cm. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Venue: Stretford Civic Theatre
    Location: Great Britain
    Additional bands or artists: The Worst, John Cooper-Clark
    Main text: With Bar: Rock Against Racism Christmas Party
  - Falling Idols, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Artist: Fletcher
    Venue: Cathay de Grande
    Main text: Cathay de Grande - Sex Donkeys? Sex Donkeys! Falling Idols & others …
  - False Idols, 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Artist: Max Volume
    Venue: Mab[uhay Gardens?]
    Additional bands or artists: Justice League of America, Breakouts, Social Unrest
    Main text: Tus. [sic] 26 - Tomorrow nite - False Idols, Justice Leauge [sic] of America, Breakouts, Social Unrest
  - False Idols, 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Additional bands or artists: Justice League of America, the Roommates, the Appliances
    Main text: Tomorrow nite - False Idols, Justice League, Roommates, Appliances, plus T.B.A. - Mab - They changed America
  - False Prophets, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Venue: Folk City
    Additional bands or artists: Soviet Sex
    Main text: False Prophets - Soviet Sex
    Notes: With ms. correction of text along bottom edge.
  - Fear, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Artist: Jaime Hernandez
    Venue: Hollister Community Center
    Additional bands or artists: Channel 3, Agression, Dr. Know, Angelic Upstarts, Social Distortion, Ill Repute, MIA
    Main text: Presenting-- Fear, CH 3, Aggression, Dr Know …
    Notes: On white paper (also issued on yellow paper)
  - Fear, 1981; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Venue: Polish Auditorium
    Additional bands or artists: Circle Jerks, 45 Grave, Mentors
    Main text: A polka party to remember - Fear, Circle Jerks, 45 Grave, Mentors
  - Fear, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Main text: Dancing Waters - Fear - Video show!! - Plus-- Special guests
  - Flesh Poids, 1970-1980; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Additional bands or artists: Ivy and the Eaters, Pressure
    Main text: The ever-popular Flesh Poids along with Ivy and the Eaters and Pressure invite you to an open-air concert in honor of Badley on his birthday
  - Gang of Four, 1980; 5.5 x 4.25 in. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Venue: California Hall
    Main text: Gang of Four - Saturday November 8 - California Hall
  - Gears, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Additional bands or artists: Gun Club, 45 Grave, Legal Weapon, Ella & the Blacks, Cliché, Adolescents, Middle Class, Minutemen, Toxic Era, Krush, Slaney, Gigantor
    Main text: This week at the Vex …
  - Generation X, 1977; A4 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Venue: Marquee
    Main text: Da boss sez: Derwood is King! - Fresh - Generation X - No needle - Painless - Cool & Collected Look …
  - Germs, 1978; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Artist: Dave Gibson
    Venue: Elks Hall
    Additional bands or artists: Needles and Pins
    Main text: Love - KROQ presents Germs and Needles and Pins
    Notes: "Souvenir poster courtesy Moxie Record Co." Unclear if this indicates that this is a souvenir poster, or that a souvenir poster was available at the performance.
  - God's Heart Attack, 1978; 24 x 17 in. (Box 40)
    Additional bands or artists: Subway
    Main text: Paradiso Gehakdag … Gods Heart Attack en Subway
  - Government Issue, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Venue: Oscars Eye
    Location: Washington, DC
    Additional bands or artists: Wurm Baby, Media Disease
    Main text: Government Issue, Wurm Baby, Media Disease
  - Government Issue, 1983; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Venue: Shamus O'Brian
    Location: South El Monte, CA
    Additional bands or artists: D.R.I., Wilful Neglect, Plain Wrap
    Main text: Wednesday Aug 10 - From Washington D.C. XXXX - Government Issue with D.R.I.
  - Halo of Flies, 1980s; 11 x 17 in. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Venue: Uptown
    Location: ???
    Main text: Halof of Flies
  - Happening Press, 1967; 25 x 19 in. (Box 40)
    Artist: Wm. Weege
    Main text: In every government on earth there is some trace of human weakness …
    Notes: Situationist-related collage poster issued by Happening Press, San Francisco.
  - [Harlots of 42nd St.], 1970s; 8.5 x 14 in. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Venue: New School for Social Research
    Main text: The nation's first illustrated college pornography course arrives at the New School Oct. 3
    Notes: Double-sided flier advertising a course at the New School for Social Research.
  - Heart Attack, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Venue: Sun Valley Sportsman
    Additional bands or artists: MIA, Jerry's Kidz, Stalag 13, Justice League of America, Child Hoods
    Main text: 12XU presents - Fuck Goldenvoice go to this!!! GBH too - From NYC - Heart Attack…
  - Hoberman, Perry, 1980s; 11 x 17 in. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Venue: The Kitchen
    Main text: Perry Hoberman: Smaller than life
  - Homosexuals, The, ca. 1984; 14.5 x 19.5 in. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Main text: The Homosexuals debut album - Definately [sic] hot and wild
    Notes: Promotional poster for The Homsexuals' Record issued by Recommended Records.
  - Human Hands, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Venue: Al's Bar
    Additional bands or artists: The Meat Puppets
    Main text: Human Hands - Meat Puppets
  - I Was Lord Kitchener's Valet, ca. 1966-67; 24 x 17 in. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Venue: I Was Lord Kitchener's Valet
    Location: London
    Main text: London's first secondhand boutique - Kinky, period & military gear - I was Lord Kitchener's valet
    Notes: Poster advertising '60s London clothing store.
  - Imperial Dogs, 1985; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Venue: Cal State Long Beach Student Union
    Main text: Rock and roll overdose - The Imperial Dogs …
  - Incest Cattle, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Venue: Onklub
    Location: Silverlake, CA
    Main text: Onklub Party - Incest Cattle, Stukas Over Bedrock, Wet Willy
  - Inserts, The, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Venue: Duke's
    Location: [Austin, TX]
    Additional bands or artists: Delinquents, The Electros
    Main text: Cure found! "Changed my whole damn life!" Arrogance in motion with Inserts …
  - Jackson Zumdish, 1980; 15 x 11 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Main text: Jackson Zumdish: the future of music issue their first statement to the world: '(I wanna be) Doctor Who'
    Notes: Poster from Agro Fish records advertising Jackson Zumdish's single
  - Jam, The, 1977; 28 x 19.5 in. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Venue: Middleton Civic Hall
    Main text: The Jam - New album, new single available now
    Notes: Promotional poster for the Jam's album In the City, with gig details added to lower right corner in ms.
  - Jitters Fish, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Artist: Bizkit
    Venue: Waterloo Park
    Additional bands or artists: Max & the Make Up, New Torpedos, Jerry's Kids, Offenders, Court Reporters, Droogs, Big Boys, the Dicks
    Main text: Punk Picnic in the Park - Jitters Fish …
  - Kommunity FK, ca. 1983; 4.25 x 5 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Main text: The time has come-- Kommunity FK - The LP
  - Last, The, 1979; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Artist: Phast
    Venue: Troubadour
    Main text: Another summer's day. The Last, Ally Cats, Plimsouls
  - Last, The, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: Descendents, Green on Red
    Main text: The return of the Last and the Descendents …
  - Legal Weapon, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: Cuckoo's Nest
    Location: Costa Mesa, CA
    Additional bands or artists: The Detours
    Main text: Legal Weapon & the Detours - Cuckoo's Nest, Costa Mesa
    Notes: On pink paper.
  - Legal Weapon, 1981; 7.5 x 9.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Notes: A smaller variant of the flier above; with incorrect printed date "Friday Aug. 4" corrected in ms. to "Sept." On white paper.
  - Legal Weapon, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: Pan Andreas Theatre
    Additional bands or artists: Funeral, Dead Hippie, Modern Warfare
    Main text: Sat. March 7 9:00 PM - Legal Weapon with Funeral …
  - Legal Weapon, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: Lost Cause, the Lewd, Convicted
    Main text: The Ritz … presents Legal Weapon - X-Adolescents Frank Agnew & Steve Soto - Lost Cause - The Lewd - Convicted
  - Leila and the Snakes, 1970-1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: Alcazar Thatre
    Main text: "Dracula" - preview & Leila and the Snakes
  - Leila and the Snakes, 1977; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: The Street Punks
    Main text: Leila and the Snakes … & the Street Punks
  - Levi & the Rockats, 1970-1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Main text: Levi & the Rockets April 3rd at the Whiskey-a-go-go - Rock-a-billy to send the round and square kats k-r-a-z-y
  - Lewd, The, 1980; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: Breakouts, Mindsweeper
    Main text: The Lewd - Breakouts - Mindsweeper
  - Lewis, Jerry Lee, 1972; 24.5 x 16.75 in. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Venue: Wembley Stadium
    Additional bands or artists: Chuck Berry, Little Richard, Bo Diddley, Platters, Drifters, Coasters, Screamin Lord Sutch, Gary Glitter, the Move
    Main text: The Rock 'n' Roll Show - Wembley Stadium Aug. 5th
    Notes: The July 22, 1972 issue of Melody Maker, opened to the two-page ad for the Aug. 5, 1972 Rock 'n' Roll Show and stored with posters to prevent deterioration along the fold. This concert was an important event for McLaren and Westwood's store Let It Rock.
  - Live Skull, 1983; 8.5 x 14 in. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Main text: Live Skull: Pyramid Dec. 6
  - Lost Souls, ca. 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Location: [New York?]
    Main text: Lost Souls - Rising from the bowels of suburbia …
    Notes: No show information; likely a general promotional flier.
  - Lowe, Nick, 1976; 42 x 29.5 cm. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Main text: Sometimes in life you've got to make a decision
    Notes: Stiff Records poster for their first release, "So It Goes" by Nick Lowe.
  - Lulu Revue, 1983; 8.5 x 14 in. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Venue: No Se No
    Main text: Lulu Review at No Se No
  - Mad, The, 1978; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: 57 Club at Irving Plaza
    Additional bands or artists: Screamin' Mad George
    Main text: The Mad with Screamin' Mad Geoge - Multi-media rock show
  - Mallory, Lee, 1967; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: UC Irvine Campus Hall
    Location: Irvine, CA
    Main text: Lee Mallory sings "That's the way it's gonna be" with your gang
    Notes: Pre-punk example of Jamie Reid-style "ransom note" lettering.
  - Massey, Edith, 1970s; 8.5 x 14 in. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Venue: Nuart
    Main text: Live on Stage… Miss Edie and the Incredible Edible Eggs."
  - Mau Maus, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Artist: Orlando X
    Additional bands or artists: Channel 3, Minutemen, Caustic Cause, China White, Aggression, Saccharine Trust, Salvation Army, D.O.A., Bad Brains
    Main text: Support the only punk club before it's gone! - We have the right - Punks unite - fight together against society's bullshit!
  - Mau Maus, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: 105 Park Row
    Location: Venice, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Minutemen, Channel 3, Seditionaries, Invisible Chains
    Main text: Mau Maus + Minutemen - Ch. 3 + Seditionaries
    Notes: "Invisible Chains" added to bill in ms.
  - Mau Maus, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: Channel 3, Minutemen, Caustic Cause
    Main text: For viewing by appointment only to qualified buyers … Who's where in area industry … aims at the little guy - self-image, sexual problems - Vietnam replay? - Obsession with politics raises rhetoric to fever pitch
  - Mau Maus, 1981; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Artist: Sandoval
    Venue: Stage One
    Location: East Los Angeles, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Girl Scoutz, Kaos, Angry Samoans
    Main text: Stage One presents in concert - Mau-Maus - To slam or not to slam that is the question
  - Mentors, 1985; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: Hard Ones
    Main text: Mentors/Hard Ones
  - Mentors, 11 x 17 in. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Main text: Mentors: Get up and die
  - MIA, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: Decry, Plain Wrap, Mad Parade
    Main text: No Bones Productions presents: M.I.A. - Decry …
  - MIA, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Main text: M.I.A. Live at the Cuckoo's Next - Gigantic bon fire of sex books on Ti[…] - Panic stalks high school corridors
  - Microwaves, Los, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: Fad Mab
    Location: n.p. [TX?]
    Additional bands or artists: See Spot, Baby Buddha
    Main text: Los Microwaves, See Spot, Baby Buddha
  - Minimal Man, ca. 1980s; 8.5 x 9 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Main text: Minimal Man
    Notes: No text other than band's name; generic promotional flier.
  - Mink DeVille, 1970s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: Killewatt, Premier
    Main text: Psyclone presents - Mink De Ville
  - Minutemen, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: McCabe's
    Additional bands or artists: Wanda Coleman, Ivan E. Roth
    Main text: Wanda Coleman, Ivan E. Roth, The Minutemen - Poetry in performance and acoustic music - Two shows
  - Minutemen, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: Johanna Went
    Main text: Named historic site - Johanna Went - Minutemen -…
  - Mnemonic Devices, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: Violent Femmes
    Main text: Mnemonic Devices with Violent Femmes
  - Model Mania, 1970-1980s; 8.25 x 5.75 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: The Bullshead
    Location: Yardley, Birmingham, UK
    Additional bands or artists: Vic Vomit's White Riot
    Main text: Punk promotions' present: Brum punk band - Model Mania - live (or thereabouts! At:- the Bullshead
  - Modern Lovers, 8.5 x 16 in. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Venue: Winter Boogie
    Location: Boston, MA
    Additional bands or artists: Moe Tucker, George Thorogood, Count Viglione's Love and Flame
    Main text: The Winter Ball: Boston's Jam'n jelly boogie
    Notes: Double-sided poster; back advertises records by Moe Tucker and Count Viglione's Love and Flame.
  - Modern Lovers, 1973; 22.5 x 17.5 in. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Venue: Glouchester High School Auditorium
    Location: Gloucester, MA
    Main text: The Modern Lovers: Gloucester High…
  - Mutants, 1980s; 8.5 x 7 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: 330 Grove
    Additional bands or artists: Offs, SSI, The Contractions
    Main text: Mutants - Offs with SSI
  - Mutants, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: Sproul Plaza, UC Berkeley
    Additional bands or artists: Tazmanian Devils, Stark Hotel, Fred Horn, Oquisha Paradox, The Tenants, Sick Pleasure, The Woudz, The Fire, Red Rockers
    Main text: Sproul Plaza Free Noon Shows
    Notes: Double-sided flier; verso has "Punk Rock music quiz" and "Super Cool Fashion '81" picture.
  - Mutants, 1978; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: Steve Weizzer, The Sleepers, Negative Trend
    Main text: Mutants - Plus pecial Guest Steve Weizzer
  - Mutants, 1978; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: Plugz, Dead Kennedys
    Main text: Co-stars Mutants & Plugz
  - Mutants, 1980; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: The City
    Additional bands or artists: Contractions
    Main text: Mutants - Contractions
  - Mutants, 1980; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: Society Dog, Dead Kennedys, Offs
    Main text: The Mutants - Sat. 8:00 PM - Calif. Hall …
  - Negative Trend, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: Deaf Club
    Additional bands or artists: JJ-180, Snuky, Walking Dead
    Main text: Negative Trend, JJ180, Snuky, !Saturday …Deaf Club…
  - Nervous Gender, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: Brave Dog
    Main text: Strong silent types - Nervous Gender - An evening at Brave Dog
  - New Order, 1983; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: Florentine Gardens and Billy Barty's Roller Fantasy
    Location: Hollywood and Fullerton, CA
    Main text: Goldenvoice present New Order
  - New Order, 1981; 23.25 x 33 in. (Box 40)
    Venue: SO 36
    Location: [Berlin, Germany]
    Main text: New Order were Joy Division
  - New York Dolls, 1974; 6.5 x 4 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Additional bands or artists: GTO's, Iggy Pop, Flo & Eddie, Hollywood Stars, Michael de Barres, Zolar X, Kim Fowley, Rodney Bingenheimer, Roy Wood's Wizzard, Raspberries, Elvin Bishop, Brian Auger, Oblivion Express, Average White Band
    Main text: Hollywood Street revival and dance - "Banned from the Roxy" -- New York Dolls
    Notes: Double-sided handbill; verso advertises two other LA-area shows in Oct. '74.
  - No Crisis, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: Bard's Apollo
    Additional bands or artists: Youth Gone Mad, RF-7, Over Kill, Angry Samoans, Caustic Cause
    Main text: Uniting in order to divide America's new religious leadership are: No Crisis, Youth Gone Mad …
  - Normals, The, 1979; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Artist: P. Percy (photo)
    Venue: Jimmy's Bar, Jed's Nite Club, The Showboat
    Location: New Orleans, LA
    Main text: The Normals - Jimmy's Bar; Jed's Nite Club
  - Nosebleeds, The, 1977; A4 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: Rafters
    Main text: The Nosebleeds - Cat No. TOSH 102 - Rafters … The Nosebleeds Ain't Bin to no Music School
  - Novak, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: Keystone
    Additional bands or artists: Leila, X-Ray Ted
    Main text: Novak - Keystone Berkeley
  - Nu-Models, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Venue: Back Dor
    Additional bands or artists: Sleepers, Jo Allen and the Shapes, Das Blok
    Main text: Nu Models - Sleepers
    Notes: Double-sided flier advertising performances from Jan. 3-6th at Back Dor.
  - Nuns, The, 1976-1980; 18 x 14 in. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Artist: Edwin Heaven, C. Johnson (design), C. Simpson (photo)
    Main text: The Nuns: represented by Edwin Heaven
  - Offs, The, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Additional bands or artists: Blowdryers
    Main text: Benefit - May 21st "riot" defense fund - The Offs, Blowdryers
  - Omlits, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Venue: Bit 'a New York and Whisky A-Go-Go
    Additional bands or artists: The Runts, Vox Pop, Nervous Gender
    Main text: Omlits - Bundy Speaks - Best Damn Band I've Ever Seen!
  - Overkill, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Venue: The Barn, Dancing Waters
    Location: Los Angeles and San Pedro, CA
    Main text: Cocksure presents Overkill at the Barn …
  - Overkill, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Additional bands or artists: Angry Samoans, The Lewd, Red Brigade
    Main text: Overkill, Angry Samoans, The Lewd, Red Brigade - March 13 - Godzilla's
  - Pagans, The, 1978; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Venue: WHK Auditorium
    Location: Cleveland, OH
    Additional bands or artists: Styrene Money, Chi Pig, Lepers, Cranks
    Main text: Johnny Dromette sez: OK, Clevo! I told you about Disasto a year ago!! Now we're in default and it's time for-- Disasto 3! Pagans! Styrene Money!
  - Pariah, 1983; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Additional bands or artists: F-U's, Skoundrelz, Peace Corps
    Main text: Wednesday Aug. 24 - Pariah, F-U's, Skoundrelz, Peace Corps
  - Miscellaneous Patti Smith and Gerard Malanga (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Phranc, 1980; 8.5 x 5.25 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Venue: Club 88
    Additional bands or artists: The Contractions, The Bags
    Main text: Thursday May 29 - Phranc solo w/surprise guests plus the Contractions - smart girls from S.F. - and yer old faves the Bags
    Notes: Double-sided flier (photos on verso)
  - Plugz, The, 1978-1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Additional bands or artists: Black Flag, Circle Jerks, Mad Society
    Main text: The Plugz, Black Flag, Circle Jerks, Mad Society - Vex prod. - Live - Vern Aud.
  - Pop Group, The, 1979; A4 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Venue: Kim Philby Club
    Additional bands or artists: A Certain Ratio, Phil Diggle
    Main text: The Kim Philby Club - Deville's - Albert Sq. - The Pop Group A Certain Ration & Phil Diggle in Rolf Harr is Dead
  - Pop, Iggy, 1980s; 17 x 5.5 in. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Venue: Agora Ballroom
    Location: [Dallas, TX]
    Additional bands or artists: Joan Jett, Daulphins, Talking Heads, Rockplie, Moon Martin & the Ravens
    Main text: Agora Ballroom: Iggy Pop
  - Professionals, The, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Additional bands or artists: The Flesh Eaters, Channel 3